const booksOfMosesData = [
  { question: "Creation", answer: "Genesis 1 & 2" },
  { question: "Sin enters the world", answer: "Genesis 3" },
  { question: "The global flood", answer: "Genesis 6 & 7" },
  { question: "Promises to Abraham", answer: "Genesis 12" },
  { question: "Sodom & Gomorrah destroyed", answer: "Genesis 19" },
  { question: "Abraham sacrifices Isaac", answer: "Genesis 22" },
  { question: "Joseph sold by brothers", answer: "Genesis 37" },
  { question: "Joseph's rise to power", answer: "Genesis 41" },
  { question: "Israelites move to Egypt", answer: "Genesis 46" },
  { question: "Israelites enslaved in Egypt", answer: "Exodus 1" },
  { question: "Moses' birth", answer: "Exodus 2" },
  { question: "The burning bush", answer: "Exodus 3" },
  { question: "The ten plagues", answer: "Exodus 7-12" },
  { question: "Parting of the Red Sea", answer: "Exodus 14" },
  { question: "Ten Commandments given", answer: "Exodus 20" },
  { question: "Aaron's golden calf", answer: "Exodus 32" },
  { question: "Tabernacle completed", answer: "Exodus 40" },
  { question: "Nadab & Abihu", answer: "Leviticus 10" },
  { question: "Spies return with a bad report", answer: "Numbers 13" },
  { question: "40 years of wandering as punishment", answer: "Numbers 14" },
  { question: "Moses' sin of striking the rock", answer: "Numbers 20" },
  { question: "The bronze serpent", answer: "Numbers 21" },
  { question: "If you obey, you will be blessed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
  { question: "If you disobey, you will be cursed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
  { question: "Moses dies at 120 years old", answer: "Deuteronomy 34" },
]

const judgesData = [
  { question: "An incomplete conquest of Canaan", answer: "Judges 1" },
  { question: "Israel cycles from sin to salvation", answer: "Judges 2" },
  { question: "Othniel, Ehud, & Shamgar save Israel", answer: "Judges 3" },
  { question: "Deborah & Barak save Israel", answer: "Judges 4" },
  { question: "The Song of Deborah & Barak", answer: "Judges 5" },
  { question: "Gideon called to save Israel", answer: "Judges 6" },
  { question: "Gideon's victory with 300 soldiers", answer: "Judges 7" },
  { question: "Gideon pursues the fleeing Midianites", answer: "Judges 8" },
  { question: "Abimelech's conspiracy", answer: "Judges 9" },
  { question: "Tola & Jair save Israel", answer: "Judges 10" },
  { question: "Jephthah saves Israel", answer: "Judges 11" },
  { question: "Ibzan, Elon, & Abdon save Israel", answer: "Judges 12" },
  { question: "The birth of Samson", answer: "Judges 13" },
  { question: "Samson's Philistine wife", answer: "Judges 14" },
  { question: "Samson saves Israel", answer: "Judges 15" },
  { question: "Samson & Delilah", answer: "Judges 16" },
  { question: "Micah's idolatry & priesthood", answer: "Judges 17" },
  { question: "Danites adopt Micah's idolatry & priesthood", answer: "Judges 18" },
  { question: "Benjamites kill the Levite's concubine", answer: "Judges 19" },
  { question: "Israel wages war against the Benjamites", answer: "Judges 20" },
  { question: "Wives provided for the Benjamites", answer: "Judges 21" },
]

const matthewData = [
  { question: "Jesus' genealogy through Joseph", answer: "Matthew 1" },
  { question: "Wise men search for Jesus", answer: "Matthew 2" },
  { question: "John baptizes Jesus", answer: "Matthew 3" },
  { question: "Temptations of Jesus", answer: "Matthew 4" },
  { question: "Sermon on the Mount", answer: "Matthew 5-7" },
  { question: "Centurion's servant healed", answer: "Matthew 8" },
  { question: "Jesus forgives sins & works miracles", answer: "Matthew 9" },
  { question: "Twelve apostles chosen", answer: "Matthew 10" },
  { question: "Jesus gives true rest", answer: "Matthew 11" },
  { question: "A tree is known by its fruit", answer: "Matthew 12" },
  { question: "Parable of the sower", answer: "Matthew 13" },
  { question: "Death of John the baptizer", answer: "Matthew 14" },
  { question: "Defilement comes from within", answer: "Matthew 15" },
  { question: "Jesus is the Christ", answer: "Matthew 16" },
  { question: "Jesus' transfiguration", answer: "Matthew 17" },
  { question: "Parable of the unforgiving servant", answer: "Matthew 18" },
  { question: "Marriage, divorce, & remarriage", answer: "Matthew 19" },
  { question: "Parable of the workers in the vineyard", answer: "Matthew 20" },
  { question: "The triumphant entry", answer: "Matthew 21" },
  { question: "Parable of the wedding feast", answer: "Matthew 22" },
  { question: "Woes to the scribes & Pharisees", answer: "Matthew 23" },
  { question: "Destruction of Jerusalem", answer: "Matthew 24" },
  { question: "Judgment Day", answer: "Matthew 25" },
  { question: "Judas' betrayal", answer: "Matthew 26" },
  { question: "Death of Jesus", answer: "Matthew 27" },
  { question: "Great Commission", answer: "Matthew 28" },
]

const johnData = [
  { question: "The Word became flesh", answer: "John 1" },
  { question: "Water into wine", answer: "John 2" },
  { question: "The new birth", answer: "John 3" },
  { question: "Samaritan woman at the well", answer: "John 4" },
  { question: "Jesus heals on the Sabbath", answer: "John 5" },
  { question: "Jesus feeds 5000", answer: "John 6" },
  { question: "People disagree about Jesus", answer: "John 7" },
  { question: "Woman caught in adultery", answer: "John 8" },
  { question: "A man born blind receives sight", answer: "John 9" },
  { question: "Jesus the Good Shepherd", answer: "John 10" },
  { question: "Death & resurrection of Lazarus", answer: "John 11" },
  { question: "Jesus anointed at Bethany", answer: "John 12" },
  { question: "Washing the disciples' feet", answer: "John 13" },
  { question: "The way, the truth, & the life", answer: "John 14" },
  { question: "The true vine", answer: "John 15" },
  { question: "Preparing apostles for Jesus' departure", answer: "John 16" },
  { question: "Jesus prays for unity", answer: "John 17" },
  { question: "Jesus before Pilate", answer: "John 18" },
  { question: "Jesus mocked, crucified, & buried", answer: "John 19" },
  { question: "The risen Christ", answer: "John 20" },
  { question: "Jesus restores Peter", answer: "John 21" },
]

const genesisData = [
  { question: "Creation: overall summary", answer: "Genesis 1" },
  { question: "Creation: specifics related to mankind", answer: "Genesis 2" },
  { question: "Sin enters the world", answer: "Genesis 3" },
  { question: "Cain & Abel", answer: "Genesis 4" },
  { question: "Genealogy of Seth", answer: "Genesis 5" },
  { question: "Preparing the ark", answer: "Genesis 6" },
  { question: "The global flood", answer: "Genesis 7" },
  { question: "Exiting the ark", answer: "Genesis 8" },
  { question: "Rainbow promise", answer: "Genesis 9" },
  { question: "Genealogy of Noah", answer: "Genesis 10" },
  { question: "Tower of Babel", answer: "Genesis 11" },
  { question: "Promises to Abram", answer: "Genesis 12" },
  { question: "Abram & Lot separate", answer: "Genesis 13" },
  { question: "Lot captured & rescued", answer: "Genesis 14" },
  { question: "God's covenant with Abram", answer: "Genesis 15" },
  { question: "Hagar & Ishmael", answer: "Genesis 16" },
  { question: "The sign of the covenant", answer: "Genesis 17" },
  { question: "A son is promised", answer: "Genesis 18" },
  { question: "Sodom & Gomorrah destroyed", answer: "Genesis 19" },
  { question: "Abraham & Abimelech", answer: "Genesis 20" },
  { question: "Birth of Isaac", answer: "Genesis 21" },
  { question: "Abraham sacrifices Isaac", answer: "Genesis 22" },
  { question: "Sarah's burial", answer: "Genesis 23" },
  { question: "Finding a bride for Isaac", answer: "Genesis 24" },
  { question: "Esau sells his birthright", answer: "Genesis 25" },
  { question: "Isaac & Abimelech", answer: "Genesis 26" },
  { question: "Jacob steals Esau's blessing", answer: "Genesis 27" },
  { question: "Jacob's vow at Bethel", answer: "Genesis 28" },
  { question: "Jacob marries Leah & Rachel", answer: "Genesis 29" },
  { question: "Jacob's children & animals increase", answer: "Genesis 30" },
  { question: "Jacob flees Laban", answer: "Genesis 31" },
  { question: "Gifts for Esau and wrestling with God", answer: "Genesis 32" },
  { question: "Jacob & Esau reconcile", answer: "Genesis 33" },
  { question: "Dinah & Shechem", answer: "Genesis 34" },
  { question: "Jacob returns to Bethel", answer: "Genesis 35" },
  { question: "Genealogy of Esau", answer: "Genesis 36" },
  { question: "Joseph sold by his brothers", answer: "Genesis 37" },
  { question: "Judah & Tamar", answer: "Genesis 38" },
  { question: "Joseph: slave & prisoner", answer: "Genesis 39" },
  { question: "The prisoners' dreams", answer: "Genesis 40" },
  { question: "Joseph's rise to power", answer: "Genesis 41" },
  { question: "Joseph's brothers buy grain in Egypt", answer: "Genesis 42" },
  { question: "Joseph's brothers return with Benjamin", answer: "Genesis 43" },
  { question: "Judah intercedes for Benjamin", answer: "Genesis 44" },
  { question: "Joseph reveals his identity", answer: "Genesis 45" },
  { question: "Israelites move to Egypt", answer: "Genesis 46" },
  { question: "Joseph manages the famine", answer: "Genesis 47" },
  { question: "Jacob blesses Joseph's sons", answer: "Genesis 48" },
  { question: "Jacob prophesies & dies", answer: "Genesis 49" },
  { question: "Mourning for Jacob & death of Joseph", answer: "Genesis 50" },
]

const generalData = [
  { question: "Old Testament books", answer: "Genesis, Exodus, etc." },
  { question: "New Testament books", answer: "Matthew, Mark, etc." },
  { question: "Creation", answer: "Genesis 1 & 2" },
  { question: "Love", answer: "I Corinthians 13" },
  { question: "What is the purpose of life?", answer: "To fear God & keep His commandments" },
  { question: "What is success?", answer: "Living your life for God and going to heaven" },
  { question: "What is failure?", answer: "Living your life for self and going to hell" },
  { question: "Sermon on the Mount", answer: "Matthew 5, 6, & 7" },
  { question: "Faith", answer: "Hebrews 11" },
  { question: "Heaven", answer: "Revelation 21" },
  { question: "The birth of the church", answer: "Acts 2" },
  { question: "Sin enters the world", answer: "Genesis 3" },
  { question: "What do you want to be when you grow up?", answer: "A Christian" },
  { question: "Birth of Jesus", answer: "Luke 2" },
  { question: "Death of Jesus", answer: "Matthew 27" },
  { question: "Temptations of Jesus", answer: "Matthew 4" },
  { question: "What is God's plan for marriage?", answer: "One man and one woman for life" },
  { question: "The global flood", answer: "Genesis 6 & 7" },
  { question: "Judgment Day", answer: "Matthew 25" },
  { question: "Promises to Abraham", answer: "Genesis 12" },
  { question: "Ten Commandments given", answer: "Exodus 20" },
  { question: "Ascension of Christ", answer: "Acts 1" },
  { question: "Conversion of Saul", answer: "Acts 9" },
  { question: "If you obey, you will be blessed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
  { question: "If you disobey, you will be cursed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
]

const bibleBookSummaryData = [
  { question: "Genesis", answer: "The Book of Beginnings" },
  { question: "Exodus", answer: "From Egypt to Sinai" },
  { question: "Leviticus", answer: "The Law of the Priests" },
  { question: "Numbers", answer: "The Wilderness Wanderings" },
  { question: "Deuteronomy", answer: "The Book of Remembrance" },
  { question: "Joshua", answer: "The Conquest of Canaan" },
  { question: "Judges", answer: "Cycling from Sin to Salvation" },
  { question: "Ruth", answer: "A Love Story" },
  { question: "I Samuel", answer: "Transitioning from Judges to Kings" },
  { question: "II Samuel", answer: "The Reign of David" },
  { question: "I Kings", answer: "The Kingdom United and the Kingdom Divided" },
  { question: "II Kings", answer: "The Decline and Fall of Israel and Judah" },
  { question: "I & II Chronicles", answer: "Genealogies and the History of Judah" },
  { question: "Ezra", answer: "The Second Exodus" },
  { question: "Nehemiah", answer: "Rebuilding Jerusalem's Wall" },
  { question: "Esther", answer: "God's Powerful Providence" },
  { question: "Job", answer: "From Tragedy to Triumph" },
  { question: "Psalms", answer: "A Book of Praises" },
  { question: "Proverbs", answer: "A Book of Wise Sayings" },
  { question: "Ecclesiastes", answer: "Life Without God is Vain" },
  { question: "Song of Solomon", answer: "The Beauty of Wedded Love" },
  { question: "Isaiah", answer: "God's Prophet of Doom and Deliverance" },
  { question: "Jeremiah", answer: "God's Prophet of Tears and Terror" },
  { question: "Lamentations", answer: "Jerusalem is Destroyed!" },
  { question: "Ezekiel", answer: "Prophecies of Judgment and Restoration" },
  { question: "Daniel", answer: "God Rules the Nations" },
  { question: "Hosea", answer: "The Spiritual Adultery and Judgment of Israel" },
  { question: "Joel", answer: "Repent, Judah!" },
  { question: "Amos", answer: "Judgment and Visions of the Future" },
  { question: "Obadiah", answer: "The Judgment of Edom" },
  { question: "Jonah", answer: "Delivering God's Message" },
  { question: "Micah", answer: "The Judgment of Israel and Judah" },
  { question: "Nahum", answer: "The Judgment of Ninevah" },
  { question: "Habakkuk", answer: "The Questioning Prophet" },
  { question: "Zephaniah", answer: "The Day of the Lord is Coming!" },
  { question: "Haggai", answer: "Rebuilding the Temple" },
  { question: "Zechariah", answer: "Night Visions and the Coming Messiah" },
  { question: "Malachi", answer: "The Unfaithful Priesthood and the Coming Messenger" },
  { question: "Matthew", answer: "Jesus the King" },
  { question: "Mark", answer: "Jesus the Sacrificial Servant" },
  { question: "Luke", answer: "Jesus the Son of Man" },
  { question: "John", answer: "Jesus the Son of God" },
  { question: "Acts", answer: "The Birth and Spread of Jesus' Church" },
  { question: "Romans", answer: "Justification Through the Gospel and an Obedient Faith" },
  { question: "I Corinthians", answer: "Division, Discipline, & Answering Posed Questions" },
  { question: "II Corinthians", answer: "Defending Paul's Apostleship, Holiness, and Giving" },
  { question: "Galatians", answer: "Liberty is in Christ" },
  { question: "Ephesians", answer: "The Church, the Body of Christ" },
  { question: "Philippians", answer: "To Live is Christ" },
  { question: "Colossians", answer: "Christ, the Head of the Church" },
  { question: "I Thessalonians", answer: "Encouragement and the Second Coming of Christ" },
  { question: "II Thessalonians", answer: "The Great Apostasy and Withdrawing Fellowship" },
  { question: "I Timothy", answer: "Gender and Leadership Roles & Advice to a Young Preacher" },
  { question: "II Timothy", answer: "Preach the Inspired Word of God" },
  { question: "Titus", answer: "Appointing Elders, God's Grace, and Good Works" },
  { question: "Philemon", answer: "A Plea for Reconciliation" },
  { question: "Hebrews", answer: "The Superiority of the New Covenant" },
  { question: "James", answer: "Practical Christian Living" },
  { question: "I Peter", answer: "Salvation, Submission, Suffering, and Service" },
  { question: "II Peter", answer: "Growing in Christ, False Teachers, and False Doctrines" },
  { question: "I John", answer: "God is Light, Love, and Life" },
  { question: "II John", answer: "Abide in the Doctrine of Christ" },
  { question: "III John", answer: "Walk in Truth, Be Faithful, and Diotrephes" },
  { question: "Jude", answer: "Contend Earnestly for the Faith" },
  { question: "Revelation", answer: "The Faithful in Christ will be Victorious" },
]

const attributesData = [
  { question: "God is one", answer: "Deuteronomy 6:4" },
  { question: "God is eternal", answer: "Psalm 90:2" },
  { question: "God is all-knowing", answer: "I John 3:20" },
  { question: "God is all-powerful", answer: "Jeremiah 32:17" },
  { question: "God is Spirit", answer: "John 4:24" },
  { question: "God is just", answer: "Revelation 15:3" },
  { question: "God is faithful", answer: "II Timothy 2:13" },
  { question: "God is holy", answer: "I Peter 1:15,16" },
  { question: "God is love", answer: "I John 4:8,9" },
  { question: "God is longsuffering", answer: "II Peter 3:9" },
  { question: "God is merciful", answer: "I Peter 1:3" },
  { question: "God is gracious", answer: "Psalm 116:5" },
  { question: "God is our Savior", answer: "Jude 25" },
  { question: "God is light", answer: "I John 1:5" },
  { question: "God is our helper", answer: "Psalm 46:1" },
  { question: "God is a consuming fire", answer: "Hebrews 12:29" },
]

const romansData = [
  { question: "The Gentiles need the gospel, which is God's power to save believers", answer: "Romans 1" },
  { question: "The Jews need the gospel more than the law or circumcision", answer: "Romans 2" },
  { question: "All have sinned, but atonement is available through Christ", answer: "Romans 3" },
  { question: "Like Abraham, we can be justified by faith", answer: "Romans 4" },
  { question: "Sin entered the world through Adam, but justification through Christ", answer: "Romans 5" },
  { question: "Believers are baptized to walk in new life, not old sins", answer: "Romans 6" },
  { question: "Christians are married to Christ & delivered from the law", answer: "Romans 7" },
  { question: "God's love is strong; there is no condemnation for faithful Christians", answer: "Romans 8" },
  { question: "Righteousness must be sought by faith, not by works of the law", answer: "Romans 9" },
  { question: "Jews & Gentiles can both be saved through faith in Christ", answer: "Romans 10" },
  { question: "The Gentiles have been grafted in to God's tree", answer: "Romans 11" },
  { question: "Everyday Christian living", answer: "Romans 12" },
  { question: "Submit to governing authorities", answer: "Romans 13" },
  { question: "Handling matters of indifference", answer: "Romans 14" },
  { question: "Paul plans to visit Rome", answer: "Romans 15" },
  { question: "Various greetings", answer: "Romans 16" },
]

const leviticusData = [
  { question: "The Law of the Priests", answer: "Book of Leviticus" },
  { question: "Details for various offerings", answer: "Leviticus 1 - 7" },
  { question: "Beginning of Aaron's family priesthood", answer: "Leviticus 8 & 9" },
  { question: "Nadab & Abihu", answer: "Leviticus 10" },
  { question: "Laws regarding ceremonial cleanness", answer: "Leviticus 11 - 15" },
  { question: "Day of Atonement", answer: "Leviticus 16" },
  { question: "The sanctity of blood", answer: "Leviticus 17" },
  { question: "Laws regarding moral issues", answer: "Leviticus 18 - 20" },
  { question: "Feast days, Sabbath year, & Jubilee", answer: "Leviticus 23 - 25" },
  {
    question: "If you obey, you will be blessed; if you disobey, you will be cursed (cf. Deut. 28)",
    answer: "Leviticus 26",
  },
]

const numbersData = [
  { question: "The Wilderness Wanderings", answer: "Book of Numbers" },
  { question: "The first census", answer: "Numbers 1 - 4" },
  { question: "Nazirite vow", answer: "Numbers 6" },
  { question: "Pillar of cloud & fire", answer: "Numbers 9" },
  { question: "Departing Mt. Sinai", answer: "Numbers 10" },
  { question: "Quail for the complainers", answer: "Numbers 11" },
  { question: "Miriam's jealousy", answer: "Numbers 12" },
  { question: "Spies return with a bad report", answer: "Numbers 13" },
  { question: "40 years of wandering as punishment", answer: "Numbers 14" },
  { question: "Sabbath violator", answer: "Numbers 15" },
  { question: "Korah's rebellion", answer: "Numbers 16" },
  { question: "The budding of Aaron's rod", answer: "Numbers 17" },
  { question: "Moses' sin of striking the rock", answer: "Numbers 20" },
  { question: "The bronze serpent", answer: "Numbers 21" },
  { question: "Balaam & Balak", answer: "Numbers 22 - 24" },
  { question: "Harlotry with Moab", answer: "Numbers 25" },
  { question: "The second census", answer: "Numbers 26" },
  { question: "Appointment of Joshua", answer: "Numbers 27" },
  { question: "The inheritance of the 2 1/2 tribes", answer: "Numbers 32" },
  { question: "Dividing the land of Canaan", answer: "Numbers 34" },
  { question: "Cities of refuge", answer: "Numbers 35" },
]

const joshuaData = [
  { question: "Prepare to possess Canaan", answer: "Joshua 1" },
  { question: "Rahab and the spies", answer: "Joshua 2" },
  { question: "Crossing the Jordan on dry ground", answer: "Joshua 3" },
  { question: "Memorial stones", answer: "Joshua 4" },
  { question: "2nd generation circumcised", answer: "Joshua 5" },
  { question: "Destruction of Jericho", answer: "Joshua 6" },
  { question: "The sin of Achan", answer: "Joshua 7" },
  { question: "Destruction of Ai", answer: "Joshua 8" },
  { question: "Covenant with the Gibeonites", answer: "Joshua 9" },
  { question: "Conquering while the sun stood still", answer: "Joshua 10" },
  { question: "Summarizing Joshua's conquests", answer: "Joshua 11" },
  { question: "List of conquered kings", answer: "Joshua 12" },
  { question: "Land divided east of the Jordan: Reuben, Gad, & one-half of Manasseh", answer: "Joshua 13" },
  { question: "Caleb inherits Hebron", answer: "Joshua 14" },
  { question: "Land inheritance of Judah", answer: "Joshua 15" },
  { question: "Land inheritance of Ephraim", answer: "Joshua 16" },
  { question: "Land inheritance of the other half of Manasseh to the west", answer: "Joshua 17" },
  { question: "Land inheritance of Benjamin", answer: "Joshua 18" },
  { question: "Land inheritance of remaining tribes", answer: "Joshua 19" },
  { question: "Cities of refuge", answer: "Joshua 20" },
  { question: "Cities of the Levites", answer: "Joshua 21" },
  { question: "The altar by the Jordan", answer: "Joshua 22" },
  { question: "Joshua's farewell address", answer: "Joshua 23" },
  { question: "Choose whom you will serve", answer: "Joshua 24" },
]

const firstCorinthiansData = [
  { question: "Unity required in Christ", answer: "1 Corinthians 1" },
  { question: "Power in the gospel, not human wisdom", answer: "1 Corinthians 2" },
  { question: "God gives the increase", answer: "1 Corinthians 3" },
  { question: "A call for humble faithfulness", answer: "1 Corinthians 4" },
  { question: "Withdrawal of fellowship", answer: "1 Corinthians 5" },
  { question: "Flee sexual immorality", answer: "1 Corinthians 6" },
  { question: "Principles of marriage", answer: "1 Corinthians 7" },
  { question: "Be sensitive to the consciences of others", answer: "1 Corinthians 8" },
  { question: "Denying self to save others", answer: "1 Corinthians 9" },
  { question: "Flee idolatry; do all to the glory of God", answer: "1 Corinthians 10" },
  { question: "Head coverings; the Lord's supper", answer: "1 Corinthians 11" },
  { question: "Many gifts & many members, but one body", answer: "1 Corinthians 12" },
  { question: "Love never fails", answer: "1 Corinthians 13" },
  { question: "Tongue-speaking & prophesying for edification", answer: "1 Corinthians 14" },
  { question: "Resurrection", answer: "1 Corinthians 15" },
  { question: "The collection", answer: "1 Corinthians 16" },
]

const secondCorinthiansData = [
  { question: "Paul explains his personal conduct", answer: "2 Corinthians 1" },
  { question: "Forgive the penitent; be the fragrance of Christ", answer: "2 Corinthians 2" },
  { question: "The gospel is a glorious system of grace", answer: "2 Corinthians 3" },
  { question: "Preach Christ boldly and persevere", answer: "2 Corinthians 4" },
  { question: "Living for Christ as a new creation", answer: "2 Corinthians 5" },
  { question: "Be separate from the world", answer: "2 Corinthians 6" },
  { question: "Godly sorrow produces repentance leading to salvation", answer: "2 Corinthians 7" },
  { question: "Giving is a proof of your love", answer: "2 Corinthians 8" },
  { question: "God loves a cheerful giver", answer: "2 Corinthians 9" },
  { question: "Don't commend yourself but glory in the Lord", answer: "2 Corinthians 10" },
  { question: "Paul's sufferings for Christ as a genuine apostle", answer: "2 Corinthians 11" },
  { question: "Paul's thorn in the flesh", answer: "2 Corinthians 12" },
  { question: "Examine yourself and avoid disqualification", answer: "2 Corinthians 13" },
]

const exodusData = [
  { question: "Israelites enslaved in Egypt", answer: "Exodus 1" },
  { question: "Birth of Moses", answer: "Exodus 2" },
  { question: "The burning bush", answer: "Exodus 3" },
  { question: "Moses reluctantly returns to Egypt", answer: "Exodus 4" },
  { question: "Pharaoh increases Israel's work", answer: "Exodus 5" },
  { question: "Israel rejects Moses' leadership", answer: "Exodus 6" },
  { question: "Plagues: Water into blood", answer: "Exodus 7" },
  { question: "Plagues: Frogs, lice, & flies", answer: "Exodus 8" },
  { question: "Plagues: Pestilence, boils, & hail", answer: "Exodus 9" },
  { question: "Plagues: Locusts & darkness", answer: "Exodus 10" },
  { question: "Death of the firstborn announced", answer: "Exodus 11" },
  { question: "Passover instituted & the final plague", answer: "Exodus 12" },
  { question: "The exodus", answer: "Exodus 13" },
  { question: "Parting of the Red Sea", answer: "Exodus 14" },
  { question: "The songs of Moses & Miriam", answer: "Exodus 15" },
  { question: "Bread from heaven", answer: "Exodus 16" },
  { question: "Water from the rock", answer: "Exodus 17" },
  { question: "Moses delegates authority", answer: "Exodus 18" },
  { question: "Israel arrives at Sinai", answer: "Exodus 19" },
  { question: "Ten Commandments given", answer: "Exodus 20" },
  { question: "Laws: Servants, violence, & animal control", answer: "Exodus 21" },
  { question: "Laws: Property & moral issues", answer: "Exodus 22" },
  { question: "Laws: Justice, Sabbaths, & feasts", answer: "Exodus 23" },
  { question: "Israel affirms the covenant", answer: "Exodus 24" },
  { question: "Instructions for the tabernacle furnishings", answer: "Exodus 25" },
  { question: "Instructions for the tabernacle structure", answer: "Exodus 26" },
  { question: "Instructions for the tabernacle court", answer: "Exodus 27" },
  { question: "Instructions for priestly garments", answer: "Exodus 28" },
  { question: "Instructions for priestly consecration", answer: "Exodus 29" },
  { question: "Miscellaneous tabernacle instructions", answer: "Exodus 30" },
  { question: "The tabernacle artisans", answer: "Exodus 31" },
  { question: "Aaron's golden calf", answer: "Exodus 32" },
  { question: "The command to leave Sinai", answer: "Exodus 33" },
  { question: "New tablets & covenant renewed", answer: "Exodus 34" },
  { question: "Giving for the tabernacle project", answer: "Exodus 35" },
  { question: "Building the tabernacle structure", answer: "Exodus 36" },
  { question: "Building the tabernacle furnishings", answer: "Exodus 37" },
  { question: "Building the tabernacle court", answer: "Exodus 38" },
  { question: "Making the priestly garments", answer: "Exodus 39" },
  { question: "Tabernacle completed", answer: "Exodus 40" },
]

const actsData = [
  { question: "Ascension of Christ", answer: "Acts 1" },
  { question: "The birth of the church", answer: "Acts 2" },
  { question: "Lame man healed", answer: "Acts 3" },
  { question: "Peter & John arrested", answer: "Acts 4" },
  { question: "Ananias & Sapphira lie & die", answer: "Acts 5" },
  { question: "Seven servants selected", answer: "Acts 6" },
  { question: "Stoning of Stephen", answer: "Acts 7" },
  { question: "Conversion of the Ethiopian eunuch", answer: "Acts 8" },
  { question: "Conversion of Saul", answer: "Acts 9" },
  { question: "Conversion of Cornelius", answer: "Acts 10" },
  { question: "They were first called Christians in Antioch", answer: "Acts 11" },
  { question: "Death of James", answer: "Acts 12" },
  { question: "Paul's first missionary journey", answer: "Acts 13 & 14" },
  { question: "Jerusalem meeting about circumcision", answer: "Acts 15" },
  { question: "Conversion of the Philippian jailer", answer: "Acts 16" },
  { question: "The philosophers in Athens", answer: "Acts 17" },
  { question: "Apollos, Aquila, & Priscilla", answer: "Acts 18" },
  { question: "Riot at Ephesus", answer: "Acts 19" },
  { question: "Encouraging the Ephesian elders", answer: "Acts 20" },
  { question: "Paul arrested in Jerusalem", answer: "Acts 21" },
  { question: "Paul recounts his conversion", answer: "Acts 22" },
  { question: "Paul before the Sanhedrin", answer: "Acts 23" },
  { question: "Paul before Felix", answer: "Acts 24" },
  { question: "Paul before Festus", answer: "Acts 25" },
  { question: "Paul before Agrippa", answer: "Acts 26" },
  { question: "Paul shipwrecked", answer: "Acts 27" },
  { question: "Paul's arrival at Rome", answer: "Acts 28" },
]

const deuteronomyData = [
  { question: "The Book of Remembrance", answer: "Book of Deuteronomy" },
  { question: "Moses recounts Israel's history", answer: "Deuteronomy 1 - 4" },
  { question: "The Ten Commandments repeated", answer: "Deuteronomy 5" },
  { question: "Love the Lord your God with all your heart", answer: "Deuteronomy 6" },
  { question: "Do not forget the Lord your God", answer: "Deuteronomy 8" },
  { question: "Remember how you provoked the Lord your God to wrath", answer: "Deuteronomy 9" },
  { question: "Circumcise the foreskin of your heart", answer: "Deuteronomy 10" },
  { question: "Choose life", answer: "Deuteronomy 30" },
  { question: "If you obey, you will be blessed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
  { question: "If you disobey, you will be cursed", answer: "Deuteronomy 28" },
  { question: "Moses' final song", answer: "Deuteronomy 32" },
  { question: "Moses blesses the tribes", answer: "Deuteronomy 33" },
  { question: "Moses dies at 120 years old", answer: "Deuteronomy 34" },
]

export {
  booksOfMosesData,
  judgesData,
  matthewData,
  johnData,
  genesisData,
  generalData,
  bibleBookSummaryData,
  attributesData,
  romansData,
  leviticusData,
  deuteronomyData,
  numbersData,
  joshuaData,
  firstCorinthiansData,
  secondCorinthiansData,
  exodusData,
  actsData,
}
